Object

Rigging TD, Technical TD, Modeling, Generalist,

Skill & Expertise

4 year in feature film, totally 15 years in visual effect. Good understanding of the complete production pipeline. Excellent knowledge of Maya and other packages. Strong rigging ability for character and vehicle. Great scripting skills with Mel and Python for developing tools and production pipeline. Excellent attention to technical details and ability to deliver accurate work.

Ability to multi-task, prioritize and problem solve. Strong listening and communication skills. An ability to focus on the big picture without losing track of the details. Maya, Python, Houdini, Softimage, ZBrush, Photoshop, Illustrate

Experience

DreamWorks	Apr. 2015 – Current	Sydney AU
	Senior Rigging	
	Feature Film "Lego Batman", "Ninjago"	
DreamWorks	Jun. 2014 – Apr.2015	Shanghai CN
	Rigging TD, Feature Film	
FlyingBark	Nov.2013 – Feb. 2014, Aug.2007 - July.2009	Sydney AU
	Rigging TD,	
	"Heidi", "Zigby", "Zeke's Pad"	
Luma Pictures	Jan.2013 – July. 2013	Melbourne AU
	Rigging TD, "I, Frankenstein"	
Dr.D Studio	May.2011-Nov.2011	Sydney AU
	Character Finaling	
	HappyFeet 2	
Plastic Wax	Nov.2004 - Dec.2006	Sydney AU

WEI HE

Rig | Model | Code

+61 4 3366 4478

weihe@WillDiGi.com

www.WillDiGi.com

weihe@WillDiGi.com

Education

CGCG

Computer Science and Programming	Current	MIT, Edx Online
C++ Object Orient Programming	2010	UTS, Sydney AU
Master of Art – Time based Art	2005-2007	UNSW, Sydney AU
Bachelor of Mechanical Engineering	1993-1998	Tongji,Shanghai CN

Rigging TD, Modeling, FX, Mo-cap Data

Rigging TD, Animator, Generalist

Shanghai CN

Dec.1999 - Oct.2004